review_id,review_text,sentiment,sentiment_score,products,brands,all_entities
1,I absolutely love this iPhone 15 Pro! The camera quality is amazing and the battery life lasts all day. Apple really outdid themselves with this one.,positive,4,[],[],"[{'text': '15', 'label': 'CARDINAL', 'start': 30, 'end': 32, 'confidence': None}, {'text': 'all day', 'label': 'DATE', 'start': 95, 'end': 102, 'confidence': None}]"
2,The Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra is fantastic. The display is crystal clear and the S Pen works perfectly. Highly recommend this phone!,positive,5,[],"['S24 Ultra', 'the S Pen']","[{'text': 'S24 Ultra', 'label': 'PERSON', 'start': 19, 'end': 28, 'confidence': None}, {'text': 'the S Pen', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 76, 'end': 85, 'confidence': None}]"
3,This MacBook Pro M3 is incredible. The performance is blazing fast and the build quality is top-notch. Worth every penny.,positive,6,[],['This MacBook Pro M3'],"[{'text': 'This MacBook Pro M3', 'label': 'PERSON', 'start': 0, 'end': 19, 'confidence': None}]"
4,I'm disappointed with this Dell XPS laptop. The battery drains too quickly and the keyboard feels cheap. Not worth the money.,negative,-1,[],['Dell XPS'],"[{'text': 'Dell XPS', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 27, 'end': 35, 'confidence': None}]"
5,The Sony WH-1000XM5 headphones are amazing! The noise cancellation is perfect and the sound quality is outstanding. Sony did a great job.,positive,6,[],"['Sony', 'Sony']","[{'text': 'Sony', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 4, 'end': 8, 'confidence': None}, {'text': 'Sony', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 116, 'end': 120, 'confidence': None}]"
6,This Logitech MX Master 3 mouse is the best I've ever used. The ergonomics are perfect and the precision is incredible. Logitech makes quality products.,positive,4,['MX'],"['Logitech', 'Logitech']","[{'text': 'Logitech', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 5, 'end': 13, 'confidence': None}, {'text': 'MX', 'label': 'PRODUCT', 'start': 14, 'end': 16, 'confidence': None}, {'text': 'Logitech', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 120, 'end': 128, 'confidence': None}]"
7,"I hate this cheap Android tablet. It's slow, the screen is terrible, and it crashes constantly. Complete waste of money.",negative,-8,[],['Android'],"[{'text': 'Android', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 18, 'end': 25, 'confidence': None}]"
8,The Microsoft Surface Pro 9 is excellent for work. The pen input is smooth and the performance is great. Microsoft really improved this model.,positive,3,[],"['The Microsoft Surface Pro', 'Microsoft']","[{'text': 'The Microsoft Surface Pro', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 0, 'end': 25, 'confidence': None}, {'text': '9', 'label': 'CARDINAL', 'start': 26, 'end': 27, 'confidence': None}, {'text': 'Microsoft', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 105, 'end': 114, 'confidence': None}]"
9,This HP printer is a nightmare. It constantly jams and the print quality is awful. I regret buying this piece of junk.,negative,-5,[],['HP'],"[{'text': 'HP', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 5, 'end': 7, 'confidence': None}]"
10,The Canon EOS R5 camera is phenomenal. The image quality is professional-grade and the autofocus is lightning fast. Canon never disappoints.,positive,4,[],[],[]
11,I love my new Tesla Model Y! The autopilot feature is incredible and the acceleration is mind-blowing. Tesla is revolutionizing the industry.,positive,3,[],[],[]
12,"This cheap Chinese smartphone is terrible. The camera is blurry, the battery dies quickly, and it's full of bugs. Avoid at all costs.",negative,-6,[],[],"[{'text': 'Chinese', 'label': 'NORP', 'start': 11, 'end': 18, 'confidence': None}]"
13,The Apple AirPods Pro 2 are perfect. The noise cancellation is amazing and the fit is comfortable. Apple's audio products are always top quality.,positive,5,[],['Apple'],"[{'text': 'Apple', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 99, 'end': 104, 'confidence': None}]"
14,I'm not impressed with this Lenovo ThinkPad. The keyboard is mushy and the trackpad is unresponsive. Expected better from Lenovo.,negative,-3,[],['Lenovo'],"[{'text': 'Lenovo', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 122, 'end': 128, 'confidence': None}]"
15,The Google Pixel 8 Pro has an incredible camera. The AI features are impressive and the software is smooth. Google really stepped up their game.,positive,3,[],['AI'],"[{'text': '8', 'label': 'CARDINAL', 'start': 17, 'end': 18, 'confidence': None}, {'text': 'AI', 'label': 'ORG', 'start': 53, 'end': 55, 'confidence': None}]"
